<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>javascript on Perry Defayette</title>
    <link>https://perrydefayette.dev/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in javascript on Perry Defayette</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 11:08:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://perrydefayette.dev/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fetching an RSS Feed (Without a Library)</title>
      <link>https://perrydefayette.dev/posts/addingrss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 11:08:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perrydefayette.dev/posts/addingrss/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a feeble attempt to stay up to date with the news without actually reading it (that&amp;rsquo;s what people do, right?). I wanted to write something that grabbed headlines from different sources to display overtop of another project I was working on. A little research turned up RSS (Really Simple Syndication) feeds in all their 2000&amp;rsquo;s glory. I dug around some more and looked for ways to encorporate them. This was actually a little more difficult than I&amp;rsquo;d originally thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Web Worker in Codepen</title>
      <link>https://perrydefayette.dev/posts/codepenwebworker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 15:33:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perrydefayette.dev/posts/codepenwebworker/</guid>
      <description>In trying to find a way to integrate javascript projects into this blog without loading special seperate css and js files into my markdown, I came across some built-in hugo shortcode for codepen. After some tinkering I was able to embed codepen projects right into my markdown using just the slug
(as in: {{&amp;lt;codePen xxxxxxx&amp;gt;}}).
However I then ran into the issue of trying to load any generic worker.js file to get a web worker running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letterscrambler</title>
      <link>https://perrydefayette.dev/projects/letterscrambler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 15:40:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perrydefayette.dev/projects/letterscrambler/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;For lack of a better title.
This application takes some user input, checks letter validity against a pre-written array of characters (so that the worker doesn&amp;rsquo;t run forever), then summons a web worker to randomly cycle the letters until the user word/phrase is found. You can control the worker delay using the slider input.
On github.
See the Pen Letter Scrambler by Perry (@defsax) on CodePen.  The user enters their word or phrase into the text box, then presses go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOTES: Troubles Running/Linking Javascript in Hugo...</title>
      <link>https://perrydefayette.dev/posts/feb0720/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:16:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perrydefayette.dev/posts/feb0720/</guid>
      <description>Overrode theme&amp;rsquo;s head.html partial in order to add my own css and js files. Getting error on attempting to onload=&amp;quot;start()&amp;rdquo; in baseof.html:
The resource from “http://localhost:1313/projects/js/titlescript.js” was blocked due to MIME type (“text/plain”) mismatch (X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff).  It&amp;rsquo;d appear that the server is trying to load the script from the wrong directory. Changing the load directory in the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tag worked for titlescript.js but not scramble.js
Error claims that the script was blocked due to MIME type (&amp;ldquo;text/plain&amp;rdquo;) mismatch, but I&amp;rsquo;ve explicitly set type=&amp;quot;application/javascript&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>